(Howard:)I'm getting worried about Bernadette.
I'm gonna call and check on her.
(Sheldon:)The National Science Foundation
wants to give me a substantial grant.
(Raj:)-That's a big deal.
-I know.
(Sheldon:)When will this nightmare end?
(Leonard:)Hey, I get that you feel bad about
all the attention,
(Leonard:)but still, what you did is amazing.
Were really proud of you.
(Sheldon:)-I'm not.
-You're not?
(Amy:)Sheldon, I've been thinking about it,
(Amy:)and you're right,
you don't deserve any credit.
(Amy:)All you did was misread
some numbers on a table.
(Amy:)A very easy table, too.
(Amy:)Honestly, I'm embarrassed for you.
Thats the most romantic thing
I've ever heard.
(Penny:)Damn it, everyone's
better at this than me.
(Sheldon:)Congratulations, Dr. Fowler.
You just made the fort.
(Howard:)Guys, there was an accident
at Bernie's lab.
(Leonard:)My God, is she okay?
(Howard:)Yeah, but she's at the hospital
in quarantine.